<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cybernews</title>
    <link>https://thomas-iniguez-visioli.github.io/nodejs-news-feeder/feed.xml</link>
    <atom:link href="https://thomas-iniguez-visioli.github.io/nodejs-news-feeder/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
    <description>fuite de donnée enregistrée </description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:24:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <title>Node.js News</title>
      <url>https://nodejs.org/static/images/logo-hexagon-card.png</url>
      <link>https://github.com/nodejs/nodejs-news-feeder</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-12106 Insufficient argument validation in OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_rc1 allows an attacker to trigger...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Insufficient argument validation in OpenVPN 2.7_alpha1 through 2.7_rc1 allows an attacker to trigger a heap buffer over-read when parsing IP addresses | Severity UNKNOWN  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2025-12106</link>
      <guid>CVE-2025-12106</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-27232 An authenticated Zabbix Super Admin can exploit the oauth.authorize action to read arbitrary files f...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[An authenticated Zabbix Super Admin can exploit the oauth.authorize action to read arbitrary files from the webserver leading to potential confidentiality loss. | Severity UNKNOWN  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2025-27232</link>
      <guid>CVE-2025-27232</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France  LVMH  la mystérieuse demande d'enquête privée sur un média français</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LVMH n'en a visiblement pas tout à fait fini avec les missions de renseignement en eaux troubles. Depuis plusieurs mois, [...]  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https//www.intelligenceonline.fr/europe-russie/2025/12/01/lvmh--la-mysterieuse-demande-d-enquete-privee-sur-un-media-francais,110568430-art</link>
      <guid>https://www.intelligenceonline.fr/europe-russie/2025/12/01/lvmh--la-mysterieuse-demande-d-enquete-privee-sur-un-media-francais,110568430-art</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Une moto électrique Tesla ? Elon Musk dit toujours non pour une raison très personnelle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[
En réponse à une vidéo créée par IA où l'on voit Elon Musk avec une moto futuriste, le patron a réitéré son explication sur pourquoi un deux-roues électrique ne verra jamais le jour chez Tesla.
  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https//www.numerama.com/vroom/2131681-une-moto-electrique-tesla-elon-musk-dit-toujours-non-pour-une-raison-tres-personnelle.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.numerama.com/vroom/2131681-une-moto-electrique-tesla-elon-musk-dit-toujours-non-pour-une-raison-tres-personnelle.html</guid>
      <category><![CDATA[Moto électrique]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Vroom]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[deux-roues]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Tesla]]></category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starship vol 12  l’immense défi industriel de SpaceX après l’explosion du booster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[
À la suite de l'explosion du tout premier booster de génération « block 3 » (le propulseur B18), SpaceX se trouve dans une course contre-la-montre inhabituelle. Pour tenir la date critique du vol 12 du Starship prévu début 2026, l'entreprise américaine doit réussir une prouesse industrielle.
  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https//www.numerama.com/sciences/2131759-starship-vol-12-limmense-defi-industriel-de-spacex-apres-lexplosion-du-booster.html</link>
      <guid>https://www.numerama.com/sciences/2131759-starship-vol-12-limmense-defi-industriel-de-spacex-apres-lexplosion-du-booster.html</guid>
      <category><![CDATA[Aérospatiale]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Espace]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Sciences]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Fusée]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[SpaceX]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Starship]]></category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L’astuce pour toucher l’iPhone 17 Pro Max moins cher  voici le bon plan caché</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="chapo has-text-weight-semibold mb-5">
<div>C'est la faille du système qu'il faut exploiter ce lundi. SFR propose l'<strong>iPhone 17 Pro Max</strong> avec une remise globale de <strong>330 €</strong>, mais la subtilité, c'est que cela fonctionne avec un forfait <strong>sans engagement</strong>. Vous prenez le téléphone, la remise, et vous restez libre.</div>
</div>  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https//www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/bons-plans-smartphone/2893749_lastuce-pour-toucher-liphone-17-pro-max-moins-cher-voici-le-bon-plan-cache</link>
      <guid>https://www.frandroid.com/bons-plans/bons-plans-smartphone/2893749_lastuce-pour-toucher-liphone-17-pro-max-moins-cher-voici-le-bon-plan-cache</guid>
      <category><![CDATA[Apple]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Bons plans]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Bons plans smartphones]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Marques]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Produits]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[SFR]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Smartphones]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Apple iPhone 17 Pro Max]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Cyber Monday 2025]]></category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quelles sont les meilleures montres connectées pas chères en 2025 ?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<div class="chapo has-text-weight-semibold mb-5">
<div>Vous voulez une montre connectée, mais vous n'avez pas un budget extensif ? <em>Frandroid</em> vous propose 7 modèles de montres connectées pas chères (sous les 200 euros) pour faire autant plaisir à votre poignet qu'à votre portefeuille.</div>
</div>  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https//www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1941478_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-montres-connectees-pas-cheres</link>
      <guid>https://www.frandroid.com/guide-dachat/1941478_quelles-sont-les-meilleures-montres-connectees-pas-cheres</guid>
      <category><![CDATA[Guides d'achat]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Guides d'achat objets connectés]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Montres connectées]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Produits]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Wearables]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Decathlon Fit 100]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Garmin Forerunner 55]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Huawei Watch Fit 4]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Ice-Watch ICE Smart Two]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[montre connectée]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[OnePlus Watch 2R]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Watch 4]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Watch FE]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Xiaomi Redmi Watch 4]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Xiaomi Redmi Watch 5]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Xiaomi Watch 2]]></category>
      <category><![CDATA[Xiaomi Watch S4]]></category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10602 A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. Affected by this ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /general/approve_center/list/input_form/data_picker_link.php. The manipulation of the argument dataSrc leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10602</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10602</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10605 A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been classified ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /file/request.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10605</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10605</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10607 A vulnerability was found in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as cr...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /track-result.php. The manipulation of the argument Consignment leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 7.3 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10607</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10607</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10608 A vulnerability was found in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. It has been rated as criti...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in code-projects Courier Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument txtusername leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 7.3 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10608</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10608</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10609 A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management Sy...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System Project 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file typeadd.php. The manipulation of the argument sex leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 01:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10609</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10609</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10610 A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affe...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function delProtocol of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/ProtocolService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10610</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10610</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10611 A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. This issue affects the funct...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function delProtocol of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/PrintScreenListService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 02:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10611</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10611</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10612 A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the fun...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function removeHookInvalidCourse of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/HookInvalidCourseService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10612</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10612</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10613 A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vuln...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delSystemEncryptPolicy of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/system/SystemEncryptPolicyService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10613</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10613</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10615 A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. It has been rated as critical. Affected by ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /general/approve_center/query/list/input_form/delete_data_attach.php. The manipulation of the argument RUN_ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 03:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10615</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10615</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10616 A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.9. This affects an unkno...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.9. This affects an unknown part of the file /pda/workflow/webSignSubmit.php. The manipulation of the argument saleId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10616</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10616</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10617 A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. This vulnerability affect...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pda/workflow/check_seal.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10617</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10617</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10618 A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Thi...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pda/reportshop/record_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument repid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10618</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10618</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10619 A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Affected...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pda/reportshop/next_detail.php. The manipulation of the argument repid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 04:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10619</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10619</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10620 A vulnerability was found in knightliao Disconf 2.6.36. It has been classified as critical. This aff...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in knightliao Disconf 2.6.36. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/config/list of the component Configuration Center. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 05:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10620</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10620</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-21510 Versions of the package sinatra from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Secur...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Versions of the package sinatra from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Security Decision via the X-Forwarded-Host (XFH) header. When making a request to a method with redirect applied, it is possible to trigger an Open Redirect Attack by inserting an arbitrary address into this header. If used for caching purposes, such as with servers like Nginx, or as a reverse proxy, without handling the X-Forwarded-Host header, attackers can potentially exploit Cache Poisoning or Routing-based SSRF. | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 05:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-21510</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-21510</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-47939 Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in multiple laser printers and MFPs which implement...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in multiple laser printers and MFPs which implement Ricoh Web Image Monitor. If this vulnerability is exploited, receiving a specially crafted request created and sent by an attacker may lead to arbitrary code execution and/or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. As for the details of affected product names and versions, refer to the information provided by the vendors under [References]. | CVSS Score 7.7 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 05:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-47939</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-47939</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-49501 Sysmac Studio provided by OMRON Corporation contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability. If th...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Sysmac Studio provided by OMRON Corporation contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker may access the program which is protected by Data Protection function. | CVSS Score 5.7 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 05:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-49501</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-49501</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0105 NVIDIA ConnectX Firmware contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper handling o...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NVIDIA ConnectX Firmware contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper handling of insufficient privileges issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, data tampering, and limited information disclosure. | CVSS Score 8.9 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 06:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-0105</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-0105</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-0106 NVIDIA ConnectX Host Firmware for the BlueField Data Processing Unit (DPU) contains a vulnerability ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NVIDIA ConnectX Host Firmware for the BlueField Data Processing Unit (DPU) contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an improper handling of insufficient privileges issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, data tampering, and limited information disclosure. | CVSS Score 8.7 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 06:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-0106</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-0106</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7424 The Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modifica...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of and access to data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to invoke those functions intended for admin use resulting in subscribers being able to upload csv files and view the contents of MPG projects. | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 08:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-7424</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-7424</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-9655 The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerabl...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Icon widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. | CVSS Score 6.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 08:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-9655</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-9655</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10232 The Group Chat  Video Chat by AtomChat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scri...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Group Chat  Video Chat by AtomChat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's atomchat shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. | CVSS Score 6.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 10:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10232</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10232</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10651 IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a specific parameter in the...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a specific parameter in the administrator interface, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary system files. | CVSS Score 4.9 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 10:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10651</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10651</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10652 IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a parameter for a specific ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a parameter for a specific functionality, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject JavsScript code and perform Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks. | CVSS Score 6.1 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 10:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10652</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10652</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10653 IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a specific parameter in the...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IDExpert from CHANGING Information Technology does not properly validate a specific parameter in the administrator interface, allowing remote attackers with administrative privileges to inject and execute OS commands on the server. | CVSS Score 7.2 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 10:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10653</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10653</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10367 The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor  FSE plugin for WordPress is...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor  FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file. | CVSS Score 6.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 11:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10367</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10367</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10654 A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 up to 9.3.5u.6369 and classified as critical. Affec...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK LR350 up to 9.3.5u.6369 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /formLoginAuth.htm. The manipulation of the argument authCode with the input 1 leads to authorization bypass. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 9.3.5u.6698_B20230810 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 12:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10654</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10654</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-7456 A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the `/api/v1/external-users` route of lunary-ai/lunary versi...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A SQL injection vulnerability exists in the `/api/v1/external-users` route of lunary-ai/lunary version v1.4.2. The `order by` clause of the SQL query uses `sql.unsafe` without prior sanitization, allowing for SQL injection. The `orderByClause` variable is constructed without server-side validation or sanitization, enabling an attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands. Successful exploitation can lead to complete data loss, modification, or corruption. | CVSS Score 9.8 (CRITICAL)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 12:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-7456</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-7456</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10655 A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been declared as critical. This vulne...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /pda/reportshop/new.php. The manipulation of the argument repid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10655</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10655</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37094 Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes MasterStudy LMS allows Exploiting Incorrectly ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes MasterStudy LMS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.

This issue affects MasterStudy LMS from n/a through 3.2.12. | CVSS Score 8.2 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37094</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37094</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-48270 An issue in the component /logins of oasys v1.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[An issue in the component /logins of oasys v1.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a burst attack. | CVSS Score 7.5 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-48270</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-48270</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-51406 Floodlight SDN Open Flow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to build fake LLDP pa...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Floodlight SDN Open Flow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to build fake LLDP packets that allow specific clusters to be missed by Floodlight, which in turn leads to missed hosts inside and outside the cluster. | CVSS Score 6.2 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-51406</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-51406</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-51407 Floodlight SDN OpenFlow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to construct false bro...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Floodlight SDN OpenFlow Controller v.1.2 has an issue that allows local hosts to construct false broadcast ports causing inter-host communication anomalies. | CVSS Score 6.2 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 14:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-51407</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-51407</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10656 A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been rated as critical. This issue af...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pda/meeting/apply.php. The manipulation of the argument mr_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10656</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10656</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10657 A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected is an unkno...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pda/approve_center/prcs_info.php. The manipulation of the argument RUN_ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10657</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10657</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-10658 A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected by this vulnerab...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tongda OA up to 11.10. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pda/approve_center/check_seal.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-10658</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-10658</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27524 Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate pri...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the filename parameter of the new_ticket.php component. | CVSS Score 7.1 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-27524</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-27524</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-27525 Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate pri...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Chamilo LMS v.1.11.26 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the filename parameter of the home.php component. | CVSS Score 4.6 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-27525</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-27525</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37095 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Envira Gallery Team Envira Photo Gallery allows Exploiting In...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Envira Gallery Team Envira Photo Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Envira Photo Gallery from n/a through 1.8.7.3. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37095</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37095</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37096 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Popup Box Team Popup allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Popup Box Team Popup allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Popup box from n/a through 4.5.1. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37096</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37096</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37106 Missing Authorization vulnerability in WishList Products WishList Member X allows Exploiting Incorre...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in WishList Products WishList Member X allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WishList Member X from n/a through 3.26.6 | CVSS Score 8.2 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37106</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37106</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37108 Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Wish...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in WishList Products WishList Member X allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WishList Member X from n/a through 3.26.6. | CVSS Score 7.7 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37108</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37108</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37119 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator Pro allows Exploiting Incorrect...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Uncanny Automator Pro from n/a through 5.3.0.0. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37119</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37119</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37123 Missing Authorization vulnerability in VowelWeb Ibtana allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Acce...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in VowelWeb Ibtana allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ibtana from n/a through 1.2.3.3. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37123</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37123</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37201 Missing Authorization vulnerability in javmah Woocommerce Customers Order History allows Exploiting ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in javmah Woocommerce Customers Order History allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Woocommerce Customers Order History from n/a through 5.2.2. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37201</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37201</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37203 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Laybuy Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce allows Exploi...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Laybuy Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Laybuy Payment Extension for WooCommerce from n/a through 5.3.9. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37203</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37203</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37204 Missing Authorization vulnerability in PropertyHive PropertyHive allows Exploiting Incorrectly Confi...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in PropertyHive PropertyHive allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects PropertyHive from n/a through 2.0.9. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37204</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37204</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37207 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Theme4Press Demo Awesome allows Exploiting Incorrectly Config...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Theme4Press Demo Awesome allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Demo Awesome from n/a through 1.0.2. | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37207</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37207</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37209 Access Control vulnerability in Prism IT Systems User Rights Access Manager allows .

This issue aff...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Access Control vulnerability in Prism IT Systems User Rights Access Manager allows .

This issue affects User Rights Access Manager from n/a through 1.1.2. | CVSS Score 6.5 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37209</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37209</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37214 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dropshipping Guru Ali2Woo Lite Exploiting Incorrectly Configu...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dropshipping Guru Ali2Woo Lite Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels, Stored XSS.This issue affects Ali2Woo Lite from n/a through 3.3.5. | CVSS Score 6.5 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37214</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37214</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37218 Missing Authorization vulnerability in WordPress Page Builder Sandwich Team Page Builder Sandwich – ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in WordPress Page Builder Sandwich Team Page Builder Sandwich – Front-End Page Builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Page Builder Sandwich – Front-End Page Builder from n/a through 5.1.0. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37218</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37218</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37220 Missing Authorization vulnerability in OptinlyHQ Optinly allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Ac...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in OptinlyHQ Optinly allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Optinly from n/a through 1.0.18. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37220</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37220</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37226 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kanban for WordPress Kanban Boards for WordPress allows Explo...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kanban for WordPress Kanban Boards for WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Kanban Boards for WordPress from n/a through 2.5.21. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37226</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37226</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37232 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hercules Design Hercules Core allows Exploiting Incorrectly C...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hercules Design Hercules Core allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Hercules Core from n/a through 6.5. | CVSS Score 8.8 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37232</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37232</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37249 Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPEngine Inc. Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows Exploiting In...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPEngine Inc. Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Advanced Custom Fields PRO from n/a through 6.3.1. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37249</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37249</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37250 Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPEngine Inc. Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows Exploiting In...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPEngine Inc. Advanced Custom Fields PRO allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Advanced Custom Fields PRO from n/a through 6.3.1. | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37250</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37250</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37254 Missing Authorization vulnerability in mndpsingh287 File Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Confi...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in mndpsingh287 File Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects File Manager from n/a through 7.2.7. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37254</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37254</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37255 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wpmet Elements kit Elementor addons allows Accessing Function...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wpmet Elements kit Elementor addons allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Elements kit Elementor addons from n/a through 3.1.4. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37255</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37255</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37269 Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes Masterstudy Elementor Widgets allows Exploitin...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes Masterstudy Elementor Widgets allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Masterstudy Elementor Widgets from n/a through 1.2.2. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37269</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37269</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37276 Missing Authorization vulnerability in fifu.App Featured Image from URL allows Exploiting Incorrectl...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in fifu.App Featured Image from URL allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Featured Image from URL from n/a through 4.8.1. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37276</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37276</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37277 Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro allows Access...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Paid Memberships Pro from n/a through 3.0.4. | CVSS Score 7.5 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37277</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37277</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37411 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Team Emilia Projects Progress Planner allows Accessing Functi...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Team Emilia Projects Progress Planner allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Progress Planner from n/a through 0.9.1. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37411</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37411</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37415 Missing Authorization vulnerability in E2Pdf.Com allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Con...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in E2Pdf.Com allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects e2pdf from n/a through 1.20.27. | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37415</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37415</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37423 Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Auto...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Blocks allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Newspack Blocks from n/a through 3.0.8. | CVSS Score 8.5 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37423</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37423</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37425 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Blocks newspack-blocks allows Exploiting ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Blocks newspack-blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Newspack Blocks from n/a through 3.0.8. | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37425</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37425</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37427 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arraytics Timetics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured A...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arraytics Timetics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Timetics from n/a through 1.0.21. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37427</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37427</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37439 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash allows Exploiti...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash from n/a through 4.1.4.0 | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37439</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37439</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37440 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configu...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Andy Moyle Church Admin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Church Admin from n/a through 4.4.4. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37440</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37440</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37443 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic WP Job Manager - Resume Manager allows Exploiting ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic WP Job Manager - Resume Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Job Manager - Resume Manager from n/a through 2.1.0. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37443</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37443</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37444 Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPMU DEV Defender Security allows Accessing Functionality Not...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPMU DEV Defender Security allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Defender Security from n/a through 4.7.1. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37444</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37444</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37453 Missing Authorization vulnerability in ProfileGrid User Profiles ProfileGrid allows Exploiting Incor...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in ProfileGrid User Profiles ProfileGrid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ProfileGrid from n/a through 5.8.7. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37453</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37453</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37456 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Noptin Newsletter Noptin allows Accessing Functionality Not P...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Noptin Newsletter Noptin allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Noptin from n/a through 3.4.2. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37456</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37456</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37463 Missing Authorization vulnerability in CRM Perks CRM Perks Forms allows Accessing Functionality Not ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in CRM Perks CRM Perks Forms allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects CRM Perks Forms from n/a through 1.1.5. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37463</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37463</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37468 Missing Authorization vulnerability in blazethemes Newsmatic allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configure...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in blazethemes Newsmatic allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Newsmatic from n/a through 1.3.1. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37468</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37468</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37470 Missing Authorization vulnerability in WofficeIO Woffice Core allows Accessing Functionality Not Pro...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in WofficeIO Woffice Core allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Woffice Core from n/a through 5.4.8. | CVSS Score 8.2 (HIGH)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37470</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37470</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37475 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Newsletters allows Accessing Functionalit...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Newsletters allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Newspack Newsletters from n/a through 2.13.2. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37475</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37475</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37477 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Content Converter allows Exploiting Incor...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Content Converter allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Newspack Content Converter from n/a through 0.1.5. | CVSS Score 6.5 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37477</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37477</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37481 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Accessing ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects The Post Grid from n/a through 7.7.4. | CVSS Score 6.5 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37481</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37481</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37482 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Exploiting...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Post Grid from n/a through 7.7.4. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37482</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37482</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37483 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Exploiting...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Post Grid Team by RadiusTheme The Post Grid allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Post Grid from n/a through 7.7.4. | CVSS Score 5.4 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37483</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37483</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37505 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rara Themes Business One Page allows Exploiting Incorrectly C...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rara Themes Business One Page allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Business One Page from n/a through 1.2.9. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37505</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37505</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37506 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Charitable Donations  Fundraising Team Charitable allows Acc...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Charitable Donations  Fundraising Team Charitable allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Charitable from n/a through 1.8.1.7. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37506</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37506</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37510 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Charitable Donations  Fundraising Team Charitable allows Acc...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Charitable Donations  Fundraising Team Charitable allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Charitable from n/a through 1.8.1.7. | CVSS Score 6.5 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37510</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37510</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37516 Missing Authorization vulnerability in fifu.App Featured Image from URL allows Exploiting Incorrectl...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in fifu.App Featured Image from URL allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Featured Image from URL from n/a through 4.8.2. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37516</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37516</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37517 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Spectra allows Exploiting Incorrectly Config...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Spectra allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Spectra from n/a through 2.13.7. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37517</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37517</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37921 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Chained Quiz allows Exploiting Incorrectly Config...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Chained Quiz allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Chained Quiz from n/a through 1.3.2.8. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37921</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37921</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37926 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Alex Volkov WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) allows Accessing Fu...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Alex Volkov WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) from n/a through 0.6.2.9. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37926</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37926</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-37929 Missing Authorization vulnerability in solwin User Activity Log Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Co...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in solwin User Activity Log Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects User Activity Log Pro from n/a through 2.3.4. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-37929</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-37929</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38690 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Avirtum iPanorama 360 WordPress Virtual Tour Builder allows A...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Avirtum iPanorama 360 WordPress Virtual Tour Builder allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects iPanorama 360 WordPress Virtual Tour Builder from n/a through 1.8.3. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-38690</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-38690</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38695 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Martin Gibson WP GoToWebinar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Co...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Martin Gibson WP GoToWebinar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP GoToWebinar from n/a through 15.6. | CVSS Score 4.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-38695</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-38695</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38702 Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite ...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Product Delivery Date for WooCommerce – Lite from n/a through 2.7.2. | CVSS Score 5.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-38702</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-38702</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-38707 Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configur...</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper EmbedPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects EmbedPress from n/a through 4.0.4. | CVSS Score 6.3 (MEDIUM)  ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:15:00 BST</pubDate>
      <link>https//nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2024-38707</link>
      <guid>CVE-2024-38707</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>